Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997 UE.4.1.7
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 7, 1.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, June 30, 1941-March 22, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Marilyn Jackson to James Matles Regarding Finances, February 22, 1946; 2.
    - Jackson to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, February 22, 1946; 3.
    - Jackson to Barish Regarding Finances, March 1, 1946; 4.
    - Jackson to Bill Cahn Regarding Publications, March 6, 1946; 5.
    - Julia Jacobs to David Ratner Regarding Finances, June 1, 1948; 6.
    - Jacobs to Ratner Regarding Address Change, June 15, 1948; 7.
    - Jacobs to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 7, 1948; 8.
    - Jacobs to Barish Regarding Supplies, February 21, 1949; 9.
    - Jacobs to Emspak Regarding Convention Delegates, August 24, 1949; 10.
    - Jacobs to Barish Regarding Forwarded Material, March 1, 1950; 11.
    - Jacobs to Barish Regarding Finances, March 22, 1950; 12.
    - Helen James to Emspak Regarding Finances, Novemer 28, 1944; 13.
    - David Kanes to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 16, 1943; 14.
    - Kanes to Leo Jandreau Regarding Requested Materials, January 6, 1944; 15.
    - Kanes to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 13, 1944; 16.
    - Kanes to Ed Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Case, September 12, 1944; 17.
    - Kanes to Matthews Regarding Requested Materials, October 6, 1944; 18.
    - Kanes to All Locals Regarding Petitons, February 17, 1945; 19.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, September 13, 1937-February 5, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - David Kanes to UE Representatives Regarding BLS Surveys, February 20, 1945; 1.
    - Kanes to Joseph Dermody Regarding Organizer Assignment, October 25, 1945; 2.
    - Kanes to James Matles Regarding Plant-Union Interaction, November 26, 1945; 3.
    - Kanes to David Scribner Regarding Local Funds, November 26, 1945; 4.
    - Kanes to Matles Regarding Negotiations, December 2, 1945; 5.
    - Kanes to Matles Regarding Election Brief, December 15, 1945; 6.
    - Kanes to BIll Cahn Regarding Publicity, January 14, 1946; 7.
    - Kanes Letter Regarding Insurance, January 24, 1946; 8.
    - Kanes to Edward Matthews Regarding Negotiations, April 3, 1946; 9.
    - June Kaplan to David Ratner Regarding Finances, August 26, 1946; 10.
    - J. Kaplan to Ratner Regarding Personal Business, September 25, 1946; 11.
    - J. Kaplan to Julius Emspak Regarding Insurance, June 2, 1947; 12.
    - J. Kaplan to Janet Barish Regarding Personal Business, August 11, 1947; 13.
    - Louis Kaplan to Matles Regardng Publicity, July 28, 1947; 14.
    - Carl Keithley to Matles Regarding Finances, February 1, 1950; 15.
    - John Keller to James Carey Regarding Meeting, September 11, 1937; 16.
    - Albert Kendell to All Locals Regarding Senate Bill, February 5, 1953; 17.
    - K. Kirkendall to Executive Board Regarding Meeting, September 13, 1937; 18.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Contract, September 27, 1937; 19.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, October 7, 1937-January 21, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - K. Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Blacklisting, October 7, 1937; 1.
    - Kirkendall to James Carey Regarding Organizers Assignment, October 13, 1937; 2.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Election, October 16, 1937; 3.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Union Case, October 26, 1937; 4.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Publicity, October 28, 1937; 5.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Organizers Assignment, November 9, 1937; 6.
    - Kirkendall to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 10, 1937; 7.
    - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Charter, November 15, 1937; 8.
    - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Charter, November 16, 1937; 9.
    - Kirkendall to Carey Regarding Meeting, November 29, 1937; 10.
    - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Charter, November 29, 1937; 11.
    - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 18, 1937; 12.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Limo Situation, December 20, 1937; 13.
    - Kirkendall to J. Madden Regarding Union Case, December 21, 1937; 14.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Negotiations, December 23, 1937; 15.
    - Kirkendall to Carey Regarding Meeting, December 29, 1937; 16.
    - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 18, 1938; 17.
    - Kirkendall to Frank Palmer Regarding Finances, January 21, 1938; 18.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, January 22-March 10, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - K. Kirkendall to James Carey Regarding Forwarded Letter, January 22, 1938; 1.
    - Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Credentials, January 22, 1938; 2.
    - Kirkendall to Gilbert Regarding Media, January 26, 1938; 3.
    - Kirkendall to Carey Regarding Finances, February 5, 1938; 4.
    - Kirkendall to Julius Emspak Regarding Financial Report, February 5, 1938; 5.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Bargaining, February 7, 1938; 6.
    - Kirkendall to Carey Regarding Meeting, February 7, 1938; 7.
    - Kirkendall to W. Mitchell Regarding Publicity, February 9, 1938; 8.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Strike Settlement, February 10, 1938; 9.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Finances, February 16, 1938; 10.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Membership Drive, March 4, 1938; 11.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Bryan Ohio Situation, February 17, 1938; 12.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Labor Movement Unity, March 6, 1938; 13.
    - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Advertising, March 7, 1938; 14.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Organizing Drive, March 9, 1938; 15.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Dayton Situation, March 10, 1938; 16.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, March 10-May 7, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - K. Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Dayton Situation, March 10, 1938; 1.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Finances, March 12, 1938; 2.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Publicity, March 15, 1938; 3.
    - Kirkendall to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, March 21, 1938; 4.
    - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Organizer's Staff, March 22, 1938; 5.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Union Case, March 30, 1938; 6.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Finances, March 30, 1938; 7.
    - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Unorganization, March 31, 1938; 8.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Layoff, March 31, 1938; 9.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Meeting Resolutions, April 25, 1938; 10.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Charter, April 23, 1938; 11.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Works Progress Administration Organization, April 26, 1938; 12.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Elections, April 29, 1938; 13-15.
    - Kirkendall to Local Unions Regarding Finances, May 7, 1938; 16.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, April 13-August 20, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - K. Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Finances, May 9, 1938; 1.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Finances, May 18, 1938; 2.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Finances, May 19, 1938; 3.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Staff Assignments, May 27, 1938; 4.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Union Case, May 31, 1938; 5.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Staff Assessment, June 21, 1938; 6.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Campaign, June 30, 1938; 7.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Union Unity, July 8, 1938; 8.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Works Progress Administration Organization, July 23, 1938; 9.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding WPA Organization, August 20, 1938; 10.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Contract, April 13, 1938; 11.
    - Kirkendall to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, May 21, 1938; 12.
    - Kirkendall Letter Regarding Vice President's Report, May 5, 1938; 13.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Bargaining, May 1, 1938; 14.
    - Kirkendall to James Carey Regarding Publicity, March 1, 1938; 15.
    - Kirkendall to Carey Regarding Election, March 1, 1938; 16.
    - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Publicity, March 1, 1938; 17.
    - Kirkendall Letter Regarding Charter, 18.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, December 5, 1940-March 23, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Melvin Krantzler to James Matles Regarding Publicity, March 23, 1951; 1.
    - Krantzler to Matles Regarding Strike, April 3, 1951; 2.
    - William Kozma to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 21, 1950; 3.
    - Helen Kraft to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, December 5, 1940; 4.
    - Kraft to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 14, 1940; 5.
    - Joseph Kres to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, October 19, 1945; 6.
    - Kres to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, August 21, 1946; 7.
    - Kres to Clifford McAvoy Regarding Finances, September 3, 1946; 8.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Convention, August 26, 1946; 9.
    - Kres to McAvoy Regarding Finances, September 3, 1946; 10.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Insurance, September 24, 1946; 11.
    - Kres Letter Regarding Publicity, October 10, 1946; 12.
    - Kres to McAvoy Regarding Financial Records, December 3, 1946; 13.
    - Kres to Matles Regarding Contract, November 25, 1949; 14.
    - Kres to Fitzgerald Regarding Conference Board, August 31, 1950; 15.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Meeting, October 25, 1950; 16.
    - Kres to Dave Ratner Regarding Finances, November 8, 1950; 17.
    - Kres to All Locals Regarding Strike Support, November 13, 1950; 18.
    - Kres to Communications Workers Regarding Strike Support, November 13, 1950; 19.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Meeting, November 13, 1950; 20.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 20, 1950; 21.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, November 22, 1950-May 21, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Joseph Kres to All Locals Regarding Conference Resolution, November 22, 1950; 1.
    - Kres to Julius Emspak Regarding Convention, November 24, 1950; 2.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 14, 1950; 3.
    - Kres to Janet Barish Regarding Convention, December 19, 1950; 4.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Convention, December 20, 1950; 5.
    - Kres to James Matles Regarding Conference, January 15, 1951; 6.
    - Kres to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, January 15, 1951; 7.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Officer's Statment, January 15, 1951; 8.
    - Kres to Fitzgerald Regarding Campaign, February 16, 1951; 9.
    - Kres to Matles Regarding Meeting, February 20, 1951; 10.
    - Kres to All Local Presidents Regarding Resolution, February 22, 1951; 11.
    - Kres to All Locals Regarding Meeting, March 14, 1951; 12.
    - Kres to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, March 27, 1951; 13.
    - Kres to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, April 19, 1951; 14.
    - Kres to Executive Board Regarding Meeting, May 5, 1951; 15.
    - Kres to Matles Regarding Personal Affairs, May 5, 1951; 16.
    - Kres to Ford Frick Regarding Publicity, May 10, 1951; 17.
    - Kres to All Locals Regarding Finances, May 21, 1951; 18.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, June 18, 1936-January 4, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Joseph Kres to All Locals Regarding Finances, May 21, 1951; 1.
    - Kres to All Locals Regarding Delegation, May 21, 1951; 2.
    - Kres Letter Regarding Personal Affairs, May 31, 1951; 3.
    - Kres to Julius Emspak Regarding Meeting, June 26, 1951; 4.
    - Kres Letter Regarding Personal Affairs, July 10, 1951; 5.
    - Kres to James Matles Regarding Meeting, July 13, 1951; 6.
    - Kres to Matles Regarding Meeting, July 20, 1951; 7.
    - Kres to All Locals Regarding Elections, September 7, 1951; 8.
    - Kres to David Ratner Regarding Check, October 23, 1951; 9.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Meeting, October 23, 1951; 10.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 21, 1951; 11.
    - Kres to Emspak Regarding Hearings, January 4, 1952; 12.
    - William Leafgreen to W. Scott Regarding Meeting, June 18, 1936; 13.
    - Nelle Lederman to Matles Regarding Mailing Lists, February 2, 1943; 14.
    - Lederman to All Locals Regarding Publicity, February 225, 1943; 15.
    - Lederman to Emspak Regarding Publications, February 25, 1943; 16.
    - Lederman to Emspak Regarding Letter Correction, March 2, 1943; 17.
    - Lederman to Matles Regarding Conference, March 17, 1943; 18.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, March 27, 1943-March 28, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Nelle Lederman to James Matles Regarding Rally, March 27, 1943; 1.
    - Lederman to Julius Emspak Regarding Rally, April 27, 1943; 2.
    - Lederman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, May 3, 1943; 3.
    - Lederman to Emspak Regarding Minutes, May 17, 1943; 4.
    - Lederman to Matles Regarding Meeting, June 16, 1943; 5.
    - Lederman to All Washington Delegates Regarding Washington Trip, June 28, 1943; 6.
    - Lederman to Russ Nixon Regarding Meeting, July 12, 1943; 7.
    - Lederman to Matles Regarding Resolution, July 12, 1943; 8.
    - Lederman to Matles Regarding Elections, July 13, 1943; 9.
    - Lederman to Matles Regarding Rally, July 22, 1943; 10.
    - Lederman Letter Regarding War Production, July 21, 1943; 11.
    - Lederman to Matles Regarding Travel Plans, August 2, 1943; 12.
    - Lederman to Victor Decavitch Regarding Staff Position, September 7, 1943; 13.
    - Lederman to Matles Regarding Check, September 8, 1943; 14.
    - Pearl Levin to David Ratner Regarding Bill, May 13, 1946; 15.
    - Walter Lohman to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, March 28, 1949; 16.
    - Rae Lowe to Matles Regarding Staff Position, January 26, 1946; 17.
    - Lowe to Janet Barish Regarding Personal Matter, February 28, 1946; 18.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, January 29, 1946-October 31, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Hyman Lumer to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, May 20, 1947; 1.
    - Lumer to James Matles Regarding Meeting, May 20, 1947; 2.
    - Lumer to Julius Emspak Regarding Lecture, May 20, 1947; 3.
    - Lumer to Bill Cahn Regarding Publications, June 18, 1947; 4.
    - Lumer to Cahn Regarding Materials, July 15, 1947; 5.
    - Lumer to Russ Nixon Regarding Weekly Report, August 18, 1947; 6.
    - Lumer to Fannie Cohn Regarding Media, October 21, 1947; 7.
    - Lumer to David Ratner Regarding Publications, October 28, 1947; 8.
    - Lumer to Nixon Regarding Finances, December 11, 1947; 9.
    - Lumer to Cahn Regarding Publications, January 16, 1948; 10.
    - Lumer to Cahn Regarding Strike, March 2, 1948; 11.
    - Lumer to Emspak Regarding Publications, May 12, 1948; 12.
    - Lumer to All Locals Regarding Strike, September 30, 1948; 13.
    - Lumer to Cahn Regarding Materials, December 8, 1948; 14.
    - Lumer to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 31, 1948; 15.
    - Lem Markland to Matles Regarding Finances, January 29, 1946; 16.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Mailing Procedures, February 16, 1946; 17.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 26, 1946; 18.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, March 6, 1946-February 14, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Lem Markland to James Matles Regarding Staff Assignments, March 6, 1946; 1.
    - Markland to Julius Emspak Regarding Letter Copies, April 23, 1946; 2.
    - Markland to Ben Cromwell Regarding Finances, April 23, 1946; 3.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 14, 1946; 4.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Rally, June 3, 1946; 5.
    - Markland to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, June 26, 1946; 6.
    - Markland to Local Presidents Regarding Meeting, June 27, 1946; 7.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 28, 1946; 8.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Meeting, October 15, 1946; 9.
    - Markland to Fitzgerald Regarding Conference, October 24, 1946; 10.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Meeting, October 29, 1946; 11.
    - Markland to Staff Members Regarding Weekly Report, November 1, 1946; 12.
    - Markland to Locals Regarding Conference, January 30, 1947; 13.
    - Markland to Fitzgerald Regarding Conference, January 30, 1947; 14.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Negotiation Results, February 7, 1947; 15.
    - Markland to Denzel Phillips Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1947; 16.
    - Markland to Alvin Secrist Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1947; 17.
    - Markland to Alfred Zuber Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1947; 18.
    - Markland to Guy Troyan Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1947; 19.
    - Markland to Rhonda Clayton Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1947; 20.
    - Markland to Ed Uhl Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1947; 21.
    - Markland to Harry Bradley Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1947; 22.
    - Markland to R. Hart Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1947; 23.
    - Markland to Ray Cannell Regarding Constitution, February 14, 1947; 24.
    - Markland to Authur Hess Regarding Constitution, February 14, 1947; 25.
    - Markland to William Kower Regarding Constitution, February 14, 1947; 26.
    - Markland to H. Spadling Regarding Constitution, February 14, 1947; 27.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, Februrary 14-October 7, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Lem Markland to Robert Butler Regarding Constitution, February 14, 1947; 1.
    - Markland to George Braen Regarding Constitution, February 14, 1947; 2.
    - Markland to Manuel Fox Regarding Constitution, February 14, 1947; 3.
    - Markland to F. Vansickle Regarding Constitution, February 14, 1947; 4.
    - Markland to Julius Emspak Regarding Publications, April 14, 1947; 5.
    - Markland to Bill Cahn Regarding Publicity, April 16, 1947; 6.
    - Markland to Joseph Bugyesinsky Regarding Finances, April 16, 1947; 7.
    - Markland to Aaron Peter Regarding Publications, April 16, 1947; 8.
    - Markland to Ray Cannell Regarding Publications, April 16, 1947; 9.
    - Markland to Joseph Hawkins Regarding Publications, April 16, 1947; 10.
    - Markland to Edwin Smith Regarding Publications, April 16, 1947; 11.
    - Markland to Ralph Kimmet Regarding Publications, April 17, 1947; 12.
    - Markland to E. Kraft Regarding Publications, April 17, 1947; 13.
    - Markland to Joseph Kres Regarding Mailing List, April 17, 1947; 14.
    - Markland to James Matles Regarding Staff Transfer, May 14, 1947; 15.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 19, 1947; 16.
    - Markland to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, June 18, 1947; 17.
    - Markland to Jake Staas Regarding Forwarded Letter, August 14, 1947; 18.
    - Markland to David Ratner Regarding Staff, August 14, 1947; 19.
    - Markland to Barish Regarding Finances, September 8, 1947; 20.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Staff Transfers, September 15, 1947; 21.
    - Markland to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, October 7, 1947; 22.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, October 9, 1947-January 22, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Lem Markland to James Matles Regarding Contract, October 9, 1947; 1.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Staff Transfers, October 30, 1947; 2.
    - Markland to Clifford Saunders Regarding Meeting, October 30, 1947; 3.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Conference, November 6, 1947; 4.
    - Markland to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, November 18, 1947; 5.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Mailing Procedures, November 28, 1947; 6.
    - Markland to Dave Ratner Regarding Finances, November 28, 1947; 7.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Meeting, December 2, 1947; 8.
    - Markland to Ratner Regarding Finances, Decembe 3, 1947; 9.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Mailing Procedures, December 12, 1947; 10.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Meeting, December 22, 1947; 11.
    - Markland to Harry Anderson Regarding Leave of Absence, December 30, 1947; 12.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Credentials, January 5, 1948; 13.
    - Markland to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Council Statement, January 14, 1948; 14.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Credentials, January 14, 1948; 15.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Office Procedures, January 22, 1948; 16.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, January 29-September 14, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Lem Markland to Janet Barish, January 29, 1948; 1.
    - Markland to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, February 2, 1948; 2.
    - Markland to Bill Cahn Regarding Materials, February 15, 1948; 3.
    - Markland to Barish Regarding Finances, February 17, 1948; 4.
    - Markland to David Ratner Regarding Staff Change, February 24, 1948; 5.
    - Markland to General Membership Regarding Union Cases, February 25, 1948; 6.
    - Markland to Ratner Regarding Finances, March 5, 1948; 7.
    - Markland to Ratner Regarding Finances, March 12, 1948; 8.
    - Markland to Ratner Regarding Finances, April 1, 1948; 9.
    - Markland to Ratner Regarding Finances, April 15, 1948; 10.
    - Markland to Julius Emspak Regarding Meeting, April 30, 1948; 11.
    - Markland to James Matles Regarding Strike, May 1, 1948; 12.
    - Markland to Ratner Regarding Finances, May 25, 1948; 13.
    - Markland to Bebe Ober Regarding Finances, June 10, 1948; 14.
    - Markland to Ratner Regarding Finances, June 10, 1948; 15.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Meeting, June 23, 1948; 16.
    - Markland to Ratner Regarding Finances, July 6, 1948; 17.
    - Markland to Janet Barish Regarding Office Procedures, July 27, 1948; 18.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding District 7 Business, August 13, 1948; 19.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Publications, September 14, 1948; 20.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, September 29-December 2, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Lem Markland to All Locals Regarding Union Case, September 29, 1948; 1.
    - Markland to All Locals Regarding Taft-Hartley Board, September 29, 1948; 2.
    - Markland to Julius Emspak Regarding Union Case, September 30, 1948; 3.
    - Markland to James Matles Regarding Publications, October 14, 1948; 4.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Educational Classes, October 21, 1948; 5.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Class Schedule, October 21, 1948; 6.
    - Markland to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Convention, October 21, 1948; 7.
    - Markland to All Locals Regarding Union Case, November 2, 1948; 8.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 9, 1948; 9.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Class Schedule, November 15, 1948; 10.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Office Location, November 18, 1948; 11.
    - Markland to Wesley Steinhilber Regarding Publications, Decembe 2, 1948; 12.
  - District 7 Outgoing Correspondence, December 2, 1948-May 4, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Lem Markland to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Forwarded Materials, December 2, 1948; 1.
    - Markland to Robert Elsner Regarding Finances, December 13, 1948; 2.
    - Markland to Julius Emspak Regarding Forwarded Letter, December 14, 1948; 3.
    - Markland to James Matles Regarding Officers Installment, Decembe 23, 1948; 4.
    - Markland to UE Stewards Regarding Forum, December 28, 1948; 5.
    - Markland to All Locals Regarding Meeting, January 11, 1949; 6.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Finances, February 2, 1949; 7.
    - Markland to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, March 7, 1949; 8.
    - Markland to Fitzgerald Regarding Conference Board, March 9, 1949; 9.
    - Markland to All Locals Regarding Presidents Meeting, March 9, 1949; 10.
    - Markland to Fitzgerald Regarding Local Affairs, March 9, 1949; 11.
    - Markland to Fitzgerald Regarding Forwarded Letter, March 9, 1949; 12.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Materials, March 14, 1949; 13.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Meeting, March 15, 1949; 14.
    - Markland to James Carey Regarding Meeting, March 19, 1949; 15.
    - Markland to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, March 23, 1949; 16.
    - Markland to Matles Regarding Credentials, April 7, 1949; 17.
    - Markland to J. Divine Regarding Financial Procedures, April 27, 1949; 18.
    - Markland to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 28, 1949; 19.
    - Markland to Fitzgerald Regarding Rallies, April 28, 1949; 20.